people I had no idea who they were going back and forth on Zoom. And apparently the intel that was
received was people couldn't tear. tell. a lot of people couldn't tell that they were fake. So now
we're going to have customer service. Now when you go on Instagram or whatever. you're going to have
somebody trying to sell you a bunch of crap and they're going to have. during the meeting. they're
going to have these AI people that are going to be talking to you. They're going to be completely
AI generated. I would imagine within the next three or four months. there'll probably be some kind of
a. this is AI overlay having to be put out there for safety purposes. but I'm not sure who's monitoring
that channel. TikToks every day. just because I think it's amazing. What I would definitely do is
just make sure that you are. Marisol. thanks. Marisol. that you would get a safe phrase or safe word with
your family. please. Got to get that done. Don't do it in earshot of anybody. Anna. thank you. Don't do
it in earshot of anybody. Do not put yourself in a bathroom with the people that are closest to you
and turn on the faucet. turn on the shower. flush the toilet as you speak this phrase between you.
No Apple watches. no other watches. nothing like that.